<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<view>
  <tooltip>
    <target>inheritedCheckbox</target>
    <anchor>left</anchor>
    <html>Inherit monitoring</html>
  </tooltip>

  <tooltip>
    <target>monitorCheckbox</target> 
    <anchor>left</anchor>
    <html>Individually enable monitoring</html>
  </tooltip>

  <tooltip>
    <target>alertOnRestartCheckBox</target>
    <anchor>left</anchor>
    <html>Alert on restart</html>
  </tooltip>
    
  <tooltip>
    <target>eventSeverityCombo</target>
    <anchor>left</anchor>
    <html>Select event severity</html>
  </tooltip>

  <tooltip>
    <target>regexIncludeTextField</target>
    <anchor>left</anchor>
    <html>Enter a <a href="http://docs.python.org/2/library/re.html" target="_new">python regular expression</a> that will match all of the command lines that this class should monitor. Note: Grouping the matched list, minus exclusions, into sets is done using the replace ... with fields.</html>
  </tooltip>

  <tooltip>
    <target>regexExcludeTextField</target>
    <anchor>left</anchor>
    <html>Enter a <a href="http://docs.python.org/2/library/re.html" target="_new">python regular expression</a> that will exclude a list of processes from the process list matched by the include field. Examples: exclude tail, grep, cat commands that may work with files or logs with similar names.</html>
  </tooltip>

  <tooltip>
    <target>regexReplaceTextField</target>
    <anchor>left</anchor>
    <html>This field and the "With" field used in conjunction provide the ability to create mnemonic set name(s) for creating and tracking one or more process sets. Note: For backward compatibility, if these fields are both left blank, the first matching process' command line will be used for the resulting process set's name.<br/>Create a regular expression to identify the portion of the command line for each process (matched by the include or exclude regex patterns) that you want to replace with the specification in the "With" field.<br/>Simple mnemonic name example: Entering <tt>.*</tt> in the "Replace command line text" field would match the entire command line and a fixed string such as <tt>MyProc</tt> in the "With" field would create a single set for all processes and will be tracked by the mnemonic name "MyProc" instead of the full command line.<br/>Multiple process set group variable identification example: By associating regex groups with portions of the pattern string matched, you can create variables that can be used in the "With" field to dynamically create different set names based on those values. If the group(s) match different values, then a process set will be generated for each unique name generated by the "With" field if it references the group(s). An example to create a unique process set for every host name being pinged: Entering <tt>^.ping ([\w.]+)\b.</tt> in the "Replace command line text" field replaces the entire command line and provides a group for the host name or IP address that can be referenced by <tt>\1</tt> in the "With" field replacement pattern. Multiple group definitions are supported.<br/>See: <a href="http://docs.python.org/2/library/re.html" target="_new">python regular expressions</a></html>
  </tooltip>

  <tooltip>
    <target>replacementTextField</target>
    <anchor>left</anchor>
    <html>The "With" field is used to generate one or more separate mnemonic process set names by substituting its value for the portion of each process’ command line matched by the "Replace command line text" <a href="http://docs.python.org/2/library/re.html" target="_new">python regular expression</a> field. For each distinct value resulting from that substitution and the remainder of the process command line text not substituted for, a separate process set will be generated that groups all processes that result in the same name.<br/>Example 1: Replacing the entire process command line with a static (but more mnemonic) text string, results in a single set being generated with a name matching the text value.<br/>Example 2: Create set names from 2 separate group values defined in the "Replace command line text" <a href="http://docs.python.org/2/library/re.html" target="_new">python regular expression</a> field and static text.  A "With" specification of <tt>"SetName\2_\1"</tt> and 3 processes whose group 1 values match "A" and a 4th with a value of "B" and all group 2 values are "X" would result in a substring replacement and set names of <tt>"SetNameX_A"</tt> containing 3 processes and <tt>"SetNameX_B"</tt> with a single process.</html>
  </tooltip>

  <tooltip>
    <target>devicesbutton</target>
    <html>Display devices</html>
  </tooltip>

  <tooltip>
    <target>eventsbutton</target>
    <html>Display events</html>
  </tooltip>
  
  <tooltip>
    <target>saveButton</target>
    <html>Save</html>
    </tooltip>

  <tooltip>
    <target>cancelButton</target>
   <html>Cancel</html>
  </tooltip>

  
</view>
