<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<view>
  <tooltip>
    <target>lock-updates-checkbox</target>
    <title>Lock from updates</title>
    <html>Select this option to prevent updates to the selected    devices. Click <strong>Lock</strong> to save your changes.</html>
  </tooltip>

  <tooltip>
    <target>lock-deletion-checkbox</target>
    <title>Lock from deletion</title>
    <html>Select this option to prevent the selected devices from being deleted. Click <strong>Lock</strong> to save your changes.</html>
  </tooltip>

  <tooltip>
    <target>send-event-checkbox</target>
    <title>Send an event when an action is blocked</title>
    <html>Select this option to create an event when a blocked action (such as update or deletion) is attempted. Click <strong>Lock</strong> to save your changes.</html>
  </tooltip>

  <tooltip>
    <target>delete-button</target>
    <title>Remove Devices</title>
    <html>Select one or more devices, and then click to display the Remove Devices dialog.<br /><br />You can choose to remove the devices from undefined state, or delete them from the system.<br /><br />To confirm your changes, click <strong>Remove</strong>.</html>
  </tooltip>

  <tooltip>
    <target>remove-radio</target>

    <html><strong>Just remove from undefined</strong><br />Select this option to remove selected devices from undefined state.</html>
  </tooltip>

  <tooltip>
    <target>delete-radio</target>

    <html><strong>Delete completely</strong><br />Select this option to remove selected devices from the system.</html>
  </tooltip>

<!--
  <tooltip>
    <target>Devices</target>

    <html></html>
  </tooltip>
-->

<!--

  <tooltip>
    <target>Map</target>

    <html>This tooltip maps to the nav item from Locations > Details > Map. Do not use.</html>
  </tooltip>
-->

<!--
  <tooltip>
    <target>zprops</target>

    <html>This tooltip maps to Device Details > Configuration Properties. Do not use. <strong>Configuration Properties</strong><br />View and edit configuration properties for the selected device class.</html>
  </tooltip>
-->

<!--

  <tooltip>
    <target>templates</target>

    <html><strong>Monitoring Templates</strong><br />View and edit performance templates for the selected device class.</html>
  </tooltip>

  <tooltip>
    <target>organizer-events</target>

    <html></html>
  </tooltip>

-->

  <tooltip>
    <target>adddevice-button</target>

    <html><strong>Add Devices</strong><br />Click to add a device in the selected device class.</html>
  </tooltip>

  <tooltip>
    <target>actions-menu</target>

    <html>
        <strong>Actions</strong><br /><br />From this menu, you can:
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Lock devices</strong> - Prevent selected devices from being updated or deleted.</li>
            <li><strong>Reset IP</strong> - Reset the IP addresses of selected devices to the results of a DNS lookup.</li>
            <li><strong>Reset Community</strong> - Reset the SNMP community strings of selected devices.</li>
            <li><strong>Set Production State</strong> - Select a production state (Production, Pre-Production, Test, Maintenance, or Decommissioned) for selected devices.</li>
            <li><strong>Set Priority</strong> - Set a priority (from Trivial to Highest) for selected devices. Setting a priority allows you to "rank" your devices, and then use those settings to control alerts.</li>
            <li><strong>Set Collector</strong> - Select a collector for selected devices.</li>
        </ul>
    </html>
  </tooltip>

  <tooltip>
    <target>commands-menu</target>

    <html>Select one or more devices, and then select a command to run in the interface.</html>
  </tooltip>
  <tooltip>
    <target>productionState</target>

    <html>

       <title>Production State</title>
       <strong>Production State</strong>Select one or more devices, and then select a production state:
       <ul>
            <li><strong>Production</strong> -  Devices are monitored and appear on the dashboard; remote alerts are sent.</li>
            <li><strong>Pre-Production</strong> - Devices are monitored. They do not appear on the dashboard, and no remote alerts are sent.</li>
            <li><strong>Test</strong> - Devices are monitored and remote alerts are sent; device information does not appear on the dashboard.</li>
            <li><strong>Maintenance</strong> - Devices are monitored and may appear on the dashboard; no remote alerts are sent.</li>
            <li><strong>Decommissioned</strong> - Devices are not monitored and do not appear on the dashboard; no remote alerts are sent.</li>
       </ul>
         
       

</html>
  </tooltip>
</view>
