<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<help>
<!--xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx -->
<pagehelp target="Dashboard" title="Dashboard">

  <p>The Dashboard provides at-a-glance information about the status of your IT infrastructure.</p>

<p><strong>User Information Area</strong><br />
Go here to:
<ul>
  <li>Sign out of the system.</li>
  <li>Access product documentation, FAQs, and HowTos.</li>
  <li>Edit user preferences and settings, by clicking the displayed login ID.</li>
</ul>
</p>

<p><strong>Portlets</strong><br />
The main content of the Dashboard comprises <em>portlets</em>, which provide information about the system and your infrastructure.</p>

<p>To add a portlet to the Dashboard, select <strong>Add portlet</strong>. Click <img src="/++resource++pagehelp/portlet_action.png"/>, which appears at the top right corner of each portlet, to edit its settings or remove the portlet.</p>

<p>To arrange portlets, click the portlet header and drag the portlet to any location on the Dashboard. Other portlets rearrange depending on the location you drop it.</p>

<p>You also can change the Dashboard column layout to one, two, or three-column displays. For two-column display, you can additionally choose a layout that offers columns of equal or varying widths. Select <strong>Configure Layout</strong> to change the layout.</p>

</pagehelp>
<!--xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx -->
<pagehelp target="Events" title="Events">
<p>The event console is the system's central nervous system, enabling you to view and manage events. It displays the repository of all events that are detected by the system.</p>

<p><strong>Sorting Events</strong><br />
You can sort events by any column that appears in the event console. To sort events, click a column header. Clicking the header toggles between ascending and descending sort order. Filter options appear below each column header.</p>

<p><strong>Refreshing Events</strong><br />
You can refresh the list of events manually or specify that they refresh automatically. To manually refresh the view, click <strong>Refresh</strong>. You can manually refresh at any time, even if you have an automatic refresh increment specified.</p>

<p>To configure automatic refresh, select one of the time increments from the Refresh list. By default, automatic refresh is enabled and set to refresh each minute.</p>

<p><strong>Viewing Event Details</strong><br />
You can view details for any event in the system. To view details, double-click an event row.</p>

<p><strong>Tip:</strong> Do not double-click on or near the device name, component, or device class in the row. Doing this displays details about that entity, rather than information about the event.</p>

<p><strong>Managing Events</strong><br />
After making an event selection, you can:
<ul>
 <li>Acknowledge the event</li>
 <li>Close the event</li>
 <li>Reclassify an event (to associate it with a specific event class)</li>
 <li>Return the event to New status (revoke its Acknowledged status)</li>
 <li>Reopen the event</li>
</ul>
</p>

<p>You also can add an event from the event console.</p>

<p><img src="/++resource++pagehelp/Event_Console_Buttons.png"/></p>

<p><strong>Exporting Event Data</strong><br />
You can export data from the event console to a comma-separated <tt>(.csv)</tt> or XML file. To do this, select <strong>Export > CSV</strong> or <strong>Export > XML</strong> By default, the exported file is named <tt>events.</tt><em>Extension</em>.</p>

</pagehelp>
<!--xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx -->
<pagehelp target="Infrastructure" title="Infrastructure">

<p>Infrastructure provides access to:

<ul>
  <li><strong>Devices</strong> - Add, discover, classify, and authenticate devices in the system.</li>
  <li><strong>Networks</strong> - View, edit, and discover devices in a network.</li>
  <li><strong>Processes</strong> - View and edit system processes.</li>
  <li><strong>IP Services</strong> - View, organize, and edit IP services.</li>
  <li><strong>Windows Services</strong> - View, organize, and edit Windows services.</li>
  <li><strong>Network Map</strong> - View the status of devices in your network.</li>
  <li><strong>Manufacturers</strong> - View and edit information about the products in your system.</li>
</ul>
</p>

<p><strong>Devices</strong><br />
The Devices page is divided into two main areas. The <em>device list</em> shows individual devices and their status. The <em>tree view</em> (in the left panel) lets you access devices by organizer (class, group, system, or location).</p>

<p>Add devices from <img src="/++resource++pagehelp/Add_Device_Button.png"/> (Add Devices). From here, you can:

<ul>
 <li>Add a single device</li>
 <li>Add and discover multiple devices</li>
 <li>Add Cisco UCS</li>
 <li>Add vCloud Cell</li>
 <li>Add VMware infrastructure</li>
 <li>Add Cisco Nexus</li>
</ul>
</p>

<p>To move devices between organizers, select one or more devices in the list, and then drag them to the desired organizer.</p>

<p>View detailed information about all devices by clicking <strong>Details</strong> in the tree view.</p>

<p>To view details for a single device, click the device name in the list to display its overview page, and then make a selection from the left panel.</p>

<p>The <img src="/++resource++pagehelp/Action_Menu.png"/> (Action menu) is located at the bottom left of the page. Options available here vary depending on your selection. Some of the tasks you can initiate here include:

<ul>
 <li>Bind templates</li>
 <li>Reset bindings</li>
 <li>Clear geocode cache</li>
 <li>Model, rename, and delete devices</li>
 <li>Add to ZenPack</li>
</ul>
</p>

</pagehelp>
<!--xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx -->
<pagehelp target="Reports" title="Reports">
<p>The system aggregates and reports, over time, on the data you set it up to monitor. The system provides a range of defined and custom report options.</p>

<p>The Reports list appears in the tree view. Expand a list item to see available reports in that category.</p>

<p><strong>Organizing Reports</strong><br />
You can organize reports and report organizers by dragging and dropping them in the tree view. To create a report organizer, select Add Report Organizer from <img src="/++resource++pagehelp/Add_Menu.png"/> (Add Menu).</p>

<p><strong>Exporting Reports</strong><br />
You can export data from any report as a comma-separated value <tt>(.csv)</tt> file. Click <strong>Export All</strong> (located at the bottom of a report).</p>


</pagehelp>
<!--xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx -->
<pagehelp target="Advanced" title="Advanced">

<p>Advanced selections let you manage a range of system settings and objects, including:

<ul>
 <li><strong>Settings</strong> - From this area, you may be able to:</li>
   <ul>
     <li>Define commands</li>
     <li>Manage users</li>
     <li>Manage loaded ZenPacks</li>
     <li>View the jobs log</li>
     <li>Determine access to portlets</li>
     <li>Stop and start system daemons</li>
     <li>Check for updates and view software component versions</li>
     <li>Back up your system instance</li>
     <li>Configure events settings</li>
     <li>Set user interface preferences</li>
     <li>Configure LDAP</li>
   </ul>

 <li><strong>Collectors</strong> - Add and delete collectors.</li>

 <li><strong>Monitoring Templates</strong> - Define monitoring templates and their components (data sources, thresholds, and graphs).</li>

 <li><strong>MIBs</strong> - Load and manage MIBs.</li>

 <li><strong>Tuning</strong> - Tune system performance.</li>
</ul>
</p>

</pagehelp>

</help>
